(Leonard:)That'd be great. Thank you.
(Howard:)Two forty-four. Right on schedule.
(Howard:)Hey, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Oh, hello.
(Howard:)Raj and I are heading over to the genetics lab
to pet the glow-in-the-dark bunny.
- Wanna come with us?
- No, thank you.
(Raj:)You sure? They turn off the lights and it's
like a little laser show that poops all over.
(Sheldon:)I'm quite sure. Good day.
(Howard:)- Where are you going?
- Where are you going?
- We told you.
- Yeah, I just told you.
- No, you didn't.
- Your word against mine. See you in court.
- Should we follow him?
- I don't know. I'm torn.
(Raj:)I want to know where he's going but
now I kind of want to play with the bunny.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Alex.
(Howard:)- Do you know where your boss just went?
- No.
- Don't you know his schedule?
- All I know is corduroy...
(Alex:)...makes too much noise
and I have to go find quieter pants.